papaly.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Papaly

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  1. To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy. Papaly uses some third-party services including but not limited to Google's Places API. By using Papaly, you also agree to be bound by the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy).

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

papaly.com  
founders@papaly.com
